Hello friends, Namaskar,
you are heartily welcome to our channel Stock Bulletin.
Today we are going to cover the stock of ICIC LBD.
This company has recently announced its
quarter 4 results and dividend.  Stay tuned
till the end of the video to know the full story.  If you
like this video, please like and
subscribe to the channel.  So let's move
ahead in the video.  ICICI LBD General
Insurance Company has
released its audited business results for the financial year 2024-25.  The
company said that it has performed brilliantly and has
registered a tremendous increase in profits and premium growth.   The
company's gross direct premium income
stood at ₹2833 crore in FY 2025, which is
8.3% higher than ₹2476 crore in the previous financial year 2024.  This growth
is much better than the industry average of 6.2%.  If we exclude the new IDR accounting
norms, the growth rate has been 11%.
Whereas the growth of the industry has been recorded at 8.6%.
Profit
after tax in Quarter 4 saw a marginal decline of around 2%.  The
company's combined ratio in the financial year 2025 was 102%.
Whereas in the financial year 2024 it was 103%.
Excluding catastrophe losses, it
stands at 102.4% and 102.5% respectively.  Which shows extreme discipline in underwriting.  The
Board of Directors of the Company has proposed a final dividend of ₹7 per share for the financial year 2025.  The
total dividend for the full year has been 12.50
paise per share.  That's all for today's video.
Subscribe to the channel for more such market related news.